cucirca.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy -

**Cucirca.com Privacy Policy**

When we designed Cucirca.com, we placed a premium on our visitors’ privacy. Hereinafter, you will find a pack of questions and answers which can help you understand our policy regarding the confidentiality of your personal information. What do the words “Privacy Policy” really mean? It is a statement that describes which data we collect, how we gather it, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may share it. What type of information is collected while you are browsing Cucirca.com? As a general rule, there is gathered non-personal information that allows us to know how the website works, such as statistical and other analytical data from an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website.

 **Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

Is registration on Cucirca.com required or optional? You may use the website without registering. Notwithstanding, by becoming a member, you will join our family. When you choose to create an account and voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (PII), such as your name and email address, we will ask you to create a user name and password. You reckon for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and your account information. Moreover, you can build personal profiles that can be viewed by other members. Our users have the right to update or correct their personal information whenever that is necessary or delete their profile anytime.

 **Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)**

Among the non-personally identifiable information we may collect rank your Internet protocol address and information associated with your computer, browser and network to deliver services or information, verify your authority to use the website, store your preferences, provide notices and generally improve the quality of our services. In order to provide you with a better experience, when you visit Cucirca.com, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. These small text files give us information about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can configure your browser to accept or reject all or some of them, or notify you when a cookie is set. However, if you choose not to receive cookies, you can still use most of the features of our website.

 **Disclosure**

We take appropriate security measures to protect your data. Cucirca.com will not intentionally disclose personally identifiable information in your account except as specifically described in this **Privacy Policy**. Only non-personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements. However, we reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information, in accordance with applicable laws, to government agencies or other parties whose requests we reasonably consider to be justified in order to protect ourselves and our users.

 **Email**

Email addresses are used for identification, inviting new friends, for general communication and to send you notifications. To smooth the process, Cucirca.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, text searches and other attributes. Users can invite friends to join us by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Cucirca.com stores these email addresses so that the respondents may be added to the friend’s list of the member sending the invitations and also to establish relationships between users. We will not use email addresses for other purposes than those described above.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**

Cucirca.com contains links to other websites. We do not exercise control over their policies regarding the confidentiality of your personal information. Your use of websites to which we link is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on such third party websites.

 **Security**

Cucirca.com is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We have put in place suitable procedural and technological measures meant to protect your data from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

 **Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, with or without notice. However, we will inform you if there are changes which can actually affect your rights. We encourage users to be responsible regarding the confidentiality of their personal information and to check every now and then the rules stipulated by this privacy policy in order to update their preferences.
